Tomáš Mikula

UI/UX Game Design

Thanks to my experiences across fields, I see myself as a perspective candidate for UI/UX designer in the game industry.

My skillset includes knowledge of UI design, cognitive psychology, programming, and games (yes, I am a gamer!), and I am used to explaining and communicating design to technical thinkers.



Skills

- <u>UI/UX Design and visualisation</u>
- Figma/Sketch and similar design related tools
- strong programming skills in Python
- · communication with technically oriented people
- · academia experience (teaching, research, etc.)
- · attention to detail

Experience

The Box - First Person UI Demo

2023

UE5 demo with working UI and game mechanics - Behance

Dept. of Computer Science - Palacký University

2018 - present

UI/UX design, print design

User interfaces course

2018 - present

Teaching UI/UX course at Palacký university, author of lecture materials.

beecode.io 2016 - present

UI/UX design, external consultations - Unizone, Noc vědců and other projects

Education

| Ph.D. | Department of Computer Science, UPOL Relational data and cognitive psychology | 2018 - present |
|-------|--|----------------|
| MSc | Department of Computer Science, UPOL Master thesis - Award winner of Dean of the Falculty of Science UP | 2016 - 2018 |
| BSc | Department of Computer Science, UPOL | 2013 - 2016 |